Guide to the Dan Miller Photographs Collection PHOTOS.120
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Dan Miller Photographs
1964-1997
1964-1980
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Miller, Dan
PHOTOS.120
9 boxes
24,544 35mm, 120mm, and 4x5 black and white negatives documenting the activities of New York City labor unions from between 1964 and 1997.
24,544 35mm, 120mm, and 4x5 black and white negatives
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Dan Miller sent a gift of circa 194,000 black and white photographic negatives, mostly 35 mm, from between 1960-1989 in 1996; additional materials were donated in 2007. In 2009, Dan Miller sent a gift of a compact disc containing photographs shot at the 2008 Commerford Awards. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 1997.028, NPA.1996.004, NPA.2005.040, NPA.2009.005, and 2018.006.
Arrangement
Series are arranged alphabetically by client (that is, the name of the organization or individual that engaged the photographer to cover a particular event) and then chronologically within clients. The Unions series is further divided by district councils and then locals following their parent bodies. The Labor Organizations series encompasses umbrella labor bodies, as well as labor union-related or –founded organizations.
Organized into 2 series:
Missing Title
I, Unions
II, Labor Organizations.
Historical/Biographical Note
Dan Miller's career as a New York union photographer has spanned more than four decades, and is distinguished, among other things, as being the longest career of any photographer in New York labor history. Since 1959, Dan Miller has photographed the activities of numerous labor unions. Every year since 1962, Miller has photographed the annual Labor Day parade in New York City. Dan Miller's company, Miller Photography, which he shares with his son Jack Miller, continues to photograph numerous New York City labor union events and is the sole photographer for the United Federation of Teachers.
Dan Miller was born on February 2, 1922, in the Bronx, New York City. He became interested in photography at age nine, obtaining his first camera (one that developed its photographs by exposing its film to the sun) from coupons in a cereal box. Later, he began using a box camera, which he took with him wherever he went, shooting photographs for himself. Almost entirely self-taught (his only formal instruction was a two-week photography course at the New York Institute of Photography that he took as a teenager), he began his career as a freelance photographer while still in high school, working for the Parkchester Press, a Bronx newspaper. After graduating from high school he also did freelance work for The Villager, another New York City newspaper. In 1940, he took a full-time civilian job photographing weapons parts at the United States Army's Raritan Arsenal, in New Jersey. He joined the Army during World War II, enlisting in September 1942, and was almost immediately assigned to the Signal Corps in the China-Burma-India theater, where he served for three years, attaining the rank of technical sergeant. In the Signal Corps he worked in a special unit, consisting of only 35 men (most were from Hollywood, California, where they worked in motion picture studios). Headquartered in New Delhi, but traveling throughout the area, the unit's work was intelligence-related; it worked closely with the CIA's forerunner agency, the Office of Strategic Services (OSS), photographing captured documents and performing aerial photography of bomb targets. One of the unit's members was Lieutenant Arthur Rubenstein, in his civilian life head photographer for Look magazine, one of the premiere American illustrated publications. After the war, Rubenstein offered Miller a job at Look. Miller worked for Look as a laboratory technician and occasional photographer from 1951 until 1959, when he bought a house and built a darkroom and began his own freelance photography business, Dan Miller Photographer (now Miller Photographers). Miller's first client was Local 342 of the Amalgamated Meatcutters Union. Through word of mouth his business grew to include a long list of other labor unions-both national and local unions--and labor organizations, such as the New York City Central Labor Council. Labor photographer Sam Reiss was Miller's colleague and main competition.
Miller also shot for advertising agencies, liquor companies, and hospitals, and photographed social activists and politicians, including Dr. Martin Luther King, jr.,President John F. Kennedy, Senator Robert F. Kennedy, and New York Governor Nelson Rockefeller.
Not only was Miller a photographer of labor union activities, he was--almost certainly unique among freelance photographers for labor unions---a union member himself, first joining Local 966 of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, and later the Newspaper Guild.
Trade unionism and photography have held an important place not only in Miller's own life, but also in the life of his family. His daughter, Madeline, worked as a picture editor and photographer for People magazine for 26 years before retiring, and his two sons, Jack and Steve, joined Dan Miller as Miller Photography photographers. Jack Miller left Miller Photography to work for the Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union. Steve Miller continues his career as a photographer, alongside his father. Their major clients are New York City-based trade unions, liquor companies, and hospitals.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Audiotape oral history interview with Dan Miller, by Maneesha Patel, March 2006.
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of 24,544 35mm, 120mm, and 4x5 black and white negatives that span the years between 1964 and 1997 and capture New York City area organized labor at the near-peak of its influence during the mid-twentieth century and also during the era of decline in the 1980s and 1990s. Unions most heavily represented include the Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees-Local 342, the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers-Local 3, Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union, Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, and United Food and Commercial Workers.
Each series is comprised of "shoots." A shoot is a group of photographic images shot by the photographer of one event--usually, but not always, on the same day. Each shoot has a unique identifying number (selected individual images within shoots have also been assigned individual numbers). The container list for this finding aid includes a complete list of shoot-level descriptions for all the images in the Collection; note that shoot numbers are listed in the column for "item." Shoot descriptions include Miller's original captions, as well as clarifications, corrections, identifications, and additional visual details provided by the processing archivists. These additions are enclosed within square brackets, so that they may be distinguished from the original caption information. The total number of negatives in a given shoot is also indicated in brackets following each shoot description in the container list: [Total negs: #].
Selected shoots or portions of shoots have been microfilmed (R-7850) to provide reference access and must be viewed in this format; original negatives not microfilmed may also be viewed by researchers. To see a complete list of shoots from this collection that have been microfilmed, with reel and frame numbers, please contact Tamiment staff, special.collections@nyu.edu.
You can also click on the link within the shoot record itself in the container list below. Those shoots in which some (or occasionally all) negatives have been microfilmed are indicated in the Container List by: Microfilm. Researchers wishing to know if a complete shoot has been microfilmed can compare the number of images in a given shoot with the number of images from that shoot they find microfilmed.
The number of organizations and clients included in the Collection is so numerous that the following table of contents has been compiled, to provide a convenient overview (in contrast to the detailed, shoot-level descriptions in the Container List) of Collection contents:
TABLE OF CONTENTS
SERIES: UNIONS
American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME)
AFSCME, District 37; date: 1973; # of negs: 221
AFSCME, Local 375; date: 1989; # of negs: 277
AFSCME, Local 444; date: 1975 - 1988; # of negs: 162
AFSCME, Local 879; date: 1985; # of negs: 99
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; date: 1992; # of negs: 61
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; date: 1980; # of negs: 75
Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees; date: 1967 - 1989; # of negs: 947
Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees, Local 342; date: 1964 - 1969; # of negs: 6912
Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees, Local 888; date: 1971; # of negs: 8
American Federation of Musicians; date: 1989; # of negs: 86
American Federation of Musicians, Local 132; date: 1977; # of negs: 92
American Federation of Musicians, Local 802; date: 1980; # of negs: 23
American Federation of Teachers; date: 1974 - 1984; # of negs: 187
American Postal Union; date: 1989; # of negs: 80
Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 50; date: 1970 - 1975; # of negs: 375
Building Service Employees International Union, Local 307; date: 1970 - 1972; # of negs: 43
Carpenters & Joiners of America, Local 45; date: 1974; # of negs: 138
Civil Service Employees Union; date: 1996; # of negs: 210
Communications Workers of America, Local 6; date: 1995; # of negs: 1421
Federation of Catholic Teachers; date: 1980 - 1983; # of negs: 26
Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union; date: 1964 - 1975; # of negs: 2724
Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union, Local 27; date: 1969; # of negs: 20
Glaziers, Local 1087; date: 1968 - 1969; # of negs: 42
Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union - Cafeteria Employees, Local 15; date: 1964 - 1967; # of negs: 916
Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union - Cafeteria Employees, Local 302; date: 1964 - 1974; # of negs: 477
International Airline Pilots Association; date: 1989; # of negs: 189
International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Local 220; date: 1969 - 1974; # of negs: 189
International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, Local 12; date: 1994; # of negs: 122
International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Local 627; date: 1967 - 1980; # of negs: 321
International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 3; date: 1973 - 1983; # of negs: 4959
International Ladies' Garment Workers Union; date: 1975; # of negs: 9
International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, Local 32; date: 1970s; # of negs: 3
International Machinists Union; date: 1997; # of negs: 111
International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, Local 51; date: 1971 - 1989; # of negs: 736
Textile Workers Union of America; date: 1968 - 1973; # of negs: 6
United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 342; date: 1967 - 1970; # of negs: 2136
SERIES: LABOR ORGANIZATIONS
Building and Construction Trades Council; date: 1970 - 1988
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Black-and-white negatives.; New York (N.Y.).
- Series I: Unions.
  Scope and Contents note
  Shoots that have been microfilmed (R-7850) are indicated by Microfilm links under the title of those shoots in the container list. These links will open a complete list of shoots from this collection that have been microfilmed, with reel and frame numbers. (Note that in the container list below, shoot numbers are listed in the column for "item.")
  - Subseries I:A: American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, District Council 37.
    - District 37, Public Service Init., Roosevelt Hotel [Total negs: 221], Oct 8, 1973 (Box 11, Item 11692)
    - Local 444 Portraits & Group [Total negs: 42], Aug 14, 1975 (Box 12, Item 11694)
    - Local 444, Membership Meeting [Total negs: 99], May 22, 1985 (Box 12, Item 11695)
    - Local 444 Contract Meeting [Total negs: 33], Aug 28, 1985 (Box 12, Item 11696)
    - Local 444 [Total negs: 20], Mar 17, 1988 (Box 12, Item 11697)
    - Local 444 Notification [?] Meeting [Total negs: 67], Sep 14, 1988 (Box 12, Item 11698)
    - Local 375 Griffin Media [Total negs: 277], Oct 22, 1989 (Box 11, Item 11693)
  - Subseries I:B: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union.
    - Benefit Island Inn [Total negs: 75], Apr 24, 1980 (Box 2, Item 8882)
    - Olga Diaz Portrait [Total negs: 48], Jun 12, 1992 (Box 2, Item 8883)
    - Olga Diaz Portrait [Total negs: 13], Jun 12, 1992 (Box 2, Item 8884)
  - Subseries I:C: Amalgamated Meatcutters and Butcher Workmen.
    - Local 342, Cyril [?] Morris [Total negs: 15], undated (Box 19, Item 11711)
    - Local 342,Nick Abbondola [?] [photographic copies of prints] [Total negs: 7], undated (Box 20, Item 11713)
    - Local 342,Otto [?] [photographic copies of prints] [Total negs: 4], undated (Box 20, Item 11714)
    - Local 342, Red Cross Building, Amsterdam Ave. 66th St., Pensioners with Gifts to [?] [Servicemen?], Jamaica Office [Total negs: 14], undated (Box 5, Item 8978)
    - Local 342, Contract Negotiations Meetings [Total negs: 54], undated (Box 5, Item 8989)
    - Local 342,Blood Bank, Queens Membership Meeting Republic Lodge Membership Meeting, International. Hotel Portraits, Moe Jotty [?] Blood Bank, Brooklyn Office [September from 120] [Total negs: 54], Mar 16, [?] (Box 3, Item 8912)
    - Local 342,Portraits, Jam & S.T., Pensioners, Brooklyn [separated from 120] [Total negs: 14], Apr 26, [?] (Box 3, Item 8915)
    - Local 342,A & P Membership Meetings International., Republics S.T. Strike Photos, Tender Beef [Total negs: 48], Apr 17, [?] (Box 3, Item 8917)
    - Local 342,A & P Vote, Grand Union, Westbury [separated from 120] [Total negs: 17], Jun 03, [?] (Box 20, Item 11712)
    - Local 342,Membership Meetings, Photo for 5 year. Issue [separated from 120] [Total negs: 34], Sep 28, [?] (Box 2, Item 8894)
    - Local 342,Elections, Staten Island, International Hotel, Huntington, Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 59], Oct 31, [?] (Box 3, Item 8905)
    - Local 342, Membership Meeting, International Hotel, Huntington [Total negs: 59], Oct 31, [?] (Box 5, Item 8971)
    - Local 342,Election Class, Election Day [Total negs: 16], Dec 01, [?] (Box 3, Item 8932)
    - Local 342,Softball, Staten Island [Total negs: 18], May 25, 1960 (Box 1, Item 8878)
    - Local 342,Apprentice School, Cools Tour [Total negs: 13], Jan 13, 1964 (Box 2, Item 8895)
    - Local 342, International Hotel Membership Meeting [Total negs: 16], Jan 27, 1964 (Box 2, Item 8896)
    - Local 342, Membership Meeting, Manhattan Center [Total negs: 32], Feb 2, 1964 (Box 2, Item 8897)
    - Local 342, International Hotel, A & P Meeting [Total negs: 13], Apr 13, 1964 (Box 2, Item 8898)
    - Local 342, Hotel Commodore, A & P Apprentice School, French Visitors [Total negs: 22], May 13, 1964 (Box 2, Item 8899)
    - Local 342, A & P Meeting Sunnyside Huntington [Total negs: 36], Jun 2, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8900)
    - Local 342, 2nd Class Graduation [Total negs: 25], Jun 26, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8901)
    - Local 342, Tour of Thinz [?] & Great Eastern [Total negs: 20], Aug 17, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8902)
    - Local 342, International Hotel Café Meeting [separated from 120] [Total negs: 15], Sep 1, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8903)
    - Local 342, Café Meeting International Hotel [Total negs: 122], Sep 21, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8904)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduates [Total negs: 10], Nov 23, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8906)
    - Local 342, Installation Meeting International Hotel [Total negs: 22], Dec 16, 1964 (Box 3, Item 8907)
    - Local 342, Hotel Trades Council Labor Unions [Total negs: 4], May 18, 1905 (Box 3, Item 8934)
    - Local 342, Shop Steward Meeting, Independents, A & P [Total negs: 120], Feb 1, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8908)
    - Locl 342 Pensioners Meeting, Apprentice School, Staten Island, Clerk Presentation, Jamaica [?] [separated from 120] [Total negs: 47], Mar 1, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8909)
    - Local 342, Opening Staten Island Office [Total negs: 17], Mar 11, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8910)
    - Local 342, Executive Meeting Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 10], Mar 15, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8911)
    - Local 342, Membership Meeting, International, Huntington, Petition Signing, Staten Island [Total negs: 37], Mar 29, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8913)
    - Local 342, Voting Dues Increase, Huntington Brooklyn Jamaica [Total negs: 30], Apr 15, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8914)
    - Local 342, A & P Shop Stewards, Huntington, International Hotel [Total negs: 24], May 10, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8916)
    - Local 342, Clerk Presentation, Apprentice School Visitors [Total negs: 14], Jun 7, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8918)
    - Local 342, Hotel Commodore A & P Negotiation [Total negs: 16], Jun 15, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8919)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduate [Total negs: 21], Jun 18, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8920)
    - Local 342, Portraits, Huntington, Jamaica 109 [separated from 120] [Total negs: 15], Jun 28, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8921)
    - Local 342, Portraits, Moe & Toby[separated from 120] [Total negs: 12], Jul 6, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8922)
    - Local 342, International Hotel, A & P Meeting [Total negs: 16], Jul 20, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8923)
    - Local 342, A & P Meetings Staten Island International - Huntington [Total negs: 67], Jul 25, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8924)
    - Local 342, Sheraton Hotel, Queens, Community Labor Committee Rally [Total negs: 50], Sep 30, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8925)
    - Local 342, Staten Island Hospital Blood Donors [Total negs: 16], Oct 1, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8926)
    - Local 342, Political Action Meeting Huntington Portraits [Total negs: 50], Oct 4, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8927)
    - Local 342, Staten Island Political Meeting [Total negs: 23], Oct 6, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8928)
    - Local 342, Long Island Federation of Labor Convention, Concord Hotel [Total negs: 56], Oct 25, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8929)
    - Local 342, Boys Tour of Italy, New Hilton, 53rd & 6th [Total negs: 36], Nov 27, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8930)
    - Local 342, Pensioners [Total negs: 12], Dec 1, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8931)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Portraits [Total negs: 21], Dec 8, 1965 (Box 3, Item 8933)
    - Local 342, Graduation [Total negs: 32], Dec 10, 1965 (Box 4, Item 8948)
    - Local 342, Red Cross Building & Office, Apprentice School Grad. Class [Total negs: 10], May 19, 1905 (Box 5, Item 8983)
    - Local 342, International Hotel Christmas Party Meeting Apprentice School Post-Graduates TV Shot [Total negs: 37], May 19, 1905 (Box 5, Item 8984)
    - Local 342, Jamaica Office Cape [Total negs: 11], Jan 25, 1966 (Box 3, Item 8936)
    - Local 342, Pension with Local 400, Luchow's [Total negs: 8], Jan 26, 1966 (Box 3, Item 8935)
    - Local 342, Blood Bank Apprentices [Total negs: 12], Feb 2, 1966 (Box 3, Item 8937)
    - Local 342, Credit Card Meeting International Hotel [Total negs: 18], Feb 15, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8938)
    - Local 342, Labor - Management, Statler Hilton [Total negs: 27], Feb 19, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8939)
    - Local 342, Jamaica Office, Community Services, with Sid Lew [Total negs: 10], Mar 1, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8940)
    - Local 342, Senior Citizens Portraits Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 14], Mar 2, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8941)
    - Local 342, Jamaica Office, Irving Stern Meeting [Total negs: 10], Mar 4, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8942)
    - Local 342, Huntington Office, Portraits [Total negs: 10], Mar 7, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8943)
    - Local 342, International Hotel, Communication Session, Portrait - Al DePrier(Tiny) [Total negs: 33], Mar 11, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8944)
    - Local 342, Shop Stewards Meeting International Hotel Huntington. 101-188 3/14-15/1966 [Total negs: 200], Mar 14, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8945)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 42], Mar 17, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8946)
    - Local 342, Food Council, Americana Hotel [Total negs: 32], Mar 23, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8947)
    - Local 342, Membership Meeting International Huntington [Total negs: 61], Mar 29, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8949)
    - Local 342, Community Meetings, Commodore Hotel [Total negs: 11], Apr 16, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8950)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 36], Apr 29, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8951)
    - Local 342, First New Members Class, Red Cross Building [Total negs: 48], May 2, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8952)
    - Local 342, Pensioners Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 21], May 3, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8953)
    - Local 342, Pensioners Leaving for Washington, D.C. [Total negs: 7], May 9, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8954)
    - Local 342, Apprentice Graduation Class, Red Cross Building [Total negs: 21], May 23, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8955)
    - Local 342, Tri-County Labor Management Institute, Garden City Hotel [Total negs: 15], May 25, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8956)
    - Local 342, Portraits Jamaica & Huntington, International Hotel, Community Services [Total negs: 15], Jun 6, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8957)
    - Picket Line, Butch Boy, Port Jefferson, Café Winners, Raffles [?] [Total negs: 35], Jul 5, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8958)
    - Local 342, Strike Photos, Café Awards [Total negs: 25], Aug 8, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8959)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School, Safety Belts [Total negs: 12], Aug 22, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8960)
    - Local 342, Deed Signing with AAA [Total negs: 8], Sep 1, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8961)
    - Local 342, Red Cross Building, New Members [Total negs: 24], Sep 19, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8962)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Graduation [Total negs: 34], Sep 23, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8963)
    - Local 342, Political Meeting, Staten Island [Total negs: 16], Sep 25, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8964)
    - Local 342, Atlantic Service Co., Pensioners, Brooklyn, American Service Co., Brooklyn [Total negs: 65], Sep 26, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8965)
    - Local 342, Shop Stewards Political Action Meeting International Hotel [Total negs: 167], Oct 4, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8966)
    - Local 342, Apprentice School Safety Class [Total negs: 20], Oct 10, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8967)
    - Local 342, A & P Bookkeepers [?] at Huntington House, Blood Bank [Total negs: 22], Oct 25, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8968)
    - Local 342, A & P Bookkeepers, Huntington Tour [?] [Total negs: 16], Oct 25, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8969)
    - Local 342, Congressman Pike, Riverhead, Long Island [Total negs: 27], Oct 30, 1966 (Box 4, Item 8970)
    - Local 342, Lester Wolf, Huntington [Total negs: 6], Nov 2, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8972)
    - Local 342, Ground Breaking, New Building [Total negs: 33], Nov 9, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8973)
    - Local 342, Seminar, International Hotel [Total negs: 12], Nov 12, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8974)
    - Local 342, Red Cross Building, Blood Bank [?] Office [Total negs: 23], Nov 12, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8982)
    - Local 342, Independent Meeting Staten Island [Total negs: 24], Nov 13, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8975)
    - Local 342, Independent Meetings, International & Huntington [Total negs: 41], Nov 14, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8976)
    - Local 342, U.N. Foreign Policy, Orsov [?] [Total negs: 16], Nov 16, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8977)
    - Local 342, Safety Photos [Total negs: 14], Dec 6, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8979)
    - Local 342, Independent Negotiations Meeting, International Hotel [Total negs: 14], Dec 7, 1966 (Box 5, Item 8980)